[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What book did author Douglas Adams describe as the fourth book in the Hitchhiker trilogy?", "correct_answer": "So Long, and Thanks For All the Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["The Restaurant at the End of the Universe", "Life, the Universe and Everything", "The Hitchhikers Guide to the Galaxy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first person in space was Russian.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can pangolins walk on their hind legs?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ataxophobia means fear of paying taxes.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the Terminator programmed to kill in the 1984 movie The Terminator?", "correct_answer": "Sarah Connor", "incorrect_answers": ["John Connor", "Kyle Reese", "The entire human race"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To which of these essential human abilities is memory closely related?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Learning", "Understanding", "Speaking"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the unofficial national motto of Switzerland?", "correct_answer": "One for all, all for one", "incorrect_answers": ["Progress ans prosperity", "In God we trust", "Higher and stronger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to geologists, in which era do we live?", "correct_answer": "Cenozoic", "incorrect_answers": ["Mesozoic", "Simpsonian", "Quaternary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What cinematic parent-child combination has had the most visible screen success in the Top 100 List?", "correct_answer": "The Hustons - Walter, John, and Angelica", "incorrect_answers": ["The Fondas- Henry, Jane and Peter", "The Tracys - Spencer  Dick", "The Barrymores - all of em!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city is the capital of the European Union?", "correct_answer": "The EU has no official capital.", "incorrect_answers": ["Brussels", "Strasbourg", "Luxembourg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of flour is used for the preparation of the bread called Broa?", "correct_answer": "Corn flour", "incorrect_answers": ["Rice flour", "Potato flour", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which great 20th century mathematician died because he refused to eat ?", "correct_answer": "Kurt Godel", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Schatten", "Paul Erdos", "Paul Wittenberg"]}]